const data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Number("1") - 1 == 0; \rWhat is the result?',
      a: "True",
      b: "False",
      c: "NaN",
      d: "TypeError",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What is the result? \r(true + false) > 2 + true;",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "2",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is the result?\r"1" - - "1";',
      a: "0",
      b: "2",
      c: "11",
      d: '"11"',
      answer: "b",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:
        'What is the result? \r new String("This is a string") instanceof String;        ',
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the result? \r[] + [] + 'foo'.split('');        ",
      a: '"f,o,o"',
      b: "TypeError",
      c: '["f","o","o"]',
      d: '[][]["f","o","o"]',
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is the result? \r[] + [] + 'foo'.split('');",
      a: '"f, o, o"',
      b: "TypeError",
      c: '["f", "o", "o"]',
      d: '[][]["f", "o", "o"]',
      answer: "xxx",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What is the result? \rnew Array(5).toString();",
      a: '",,,,"',
      b: "[]",
      c: '"[]"',
      d: "(empty)",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "What is the result? \rString('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'What is the result? \r"This is a string" instanceof String;',
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "xxx",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question:
        "What is the result console.log(myArr); ? \rvar myArr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz']; \rmyArr.length = 0; \r myArr.push('bin');",
      a: "['foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      b: "['foo', 'bar', 'baz', 'bin']",
      c: "['bin', 'foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      d: "['bin']",
      answer: "d",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "What is the result? \rString('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "What is the result? \r10 > 9 > 8 === true;",
      a: "True",
      b: "False",
      c: "Error",
      d: "Other",
      answer: "b",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "What is the result? \rNaN === NaN;",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "b",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: 'Number("1") - 1 == 0; \rWhat is the result?',
      a: "True",
      b: "False",
      c: "NaN",
      d: "TypeError",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: "What is the result? \r(true + false) > 2 + true;",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "2",
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: 'What is the result?\r"1" - - "1";',
      a: "0",
      b: "2",
      c: "11",
      d: '"11"',
      answer: "b",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question:
        'What is the result? \r new String("This is a string") instanceof String;        ',
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: "What is the result? \r[] + [] + 'foo'.split('');        ",
      a: '"f,o,o"',
      b: "TypeError",
      c: '["f","o","o"]',
      d: '[][]["f","o","o"]',
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: "What is the result? \r[] + [] + 'foo'.split('');",
      a: '"f, o, o"',
      b: "TypeError",
      c: '["f", "o", "o"]',
      d: '[][]["f", "o", "o"]',
      answer: "xxx",
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: "What is the result? \rnew Array(5).toString();",
      a: '",,,,"',
      b: "[]",
      c: '"[]"',
      d: "(empty)",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: "What is the result? \rString('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: 'What is the result? \r"This is a string" instanceof String;',
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "xxx",
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question:
        "What is the result console.log(myArr); ? \rvar myArr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz']; \rmyArr.length = 0; \r myArr.push('bin');",
      a: "['foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      b: "['foo', 'bar', 'baz', 'bin']",
      c: "['bin', 'foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      d: "['bin']",
      answer: "d",
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: "What is the result? \rString('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: "What is the result? \r10 > 9 > 8 === true;",
      a: "True",
      b: "False",
      c: "Error",
      d: "Other",
      answer: "b",
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: "What is the result? \rNaN === NaN;",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "b",
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question:
        "What is the result console.log(myArr); ? \rvar myArr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz']; \rmyArr.length = 0; \r myArr.push('bin');",
      a: "['foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      b: "['foo', 'bar', 'baz', 'bin']",
      c: "['bin', 'foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      d: "['bin']",
      answer: "d",
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: "What is the result? \rString('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "a",
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: "What is the result? \r10 > 9 > 8 === true;",
      a: "True",
      b: "False",
      c: "Error",
      d: "Other",
      answer: "b",
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: "What is the result? \rNaN === NaN;",
      a: "true",
      b: "false",
      c: "TypeError",
      d: "NaN",
      answer: "b",
    },
  ];